=A Taste of First Love=
= طعم الحب الأول =
=Episode 15=
= الحلقة 15 =
Tell me.
أخبرني.
How long has it lasted?
كم من الوقت دامت؟
It only started
لقد بدأت فقط
after our breakup.
بعد تفككنا.
It's been five years, you know?
لقد مرت خمس سنوات ، هل تعلم؟
You're too empty inside...
أنت فارغ جدًا بالداخل ...
If so,
لو ذلك،
where did you purchase them from?
من أين اشتريتهم؟
Did you hire someone to make them for you?
هل قمت بتوظيف شخص ما ليصنعها لك؟
Of course I made them myself.
بالطبع صنعتها بنفسي.
How could I hire someone else to do this?
كيف يمكنني توظيف شخص آخر للقيام بذلك؟
Luckily, no one else saw them.
لحسن الحظ ، لم يرهم أحد.
If not, I'll be thoroughly embarrassed.
إذا لم يكن الأمر كذلك ، فسأشعر بالحرج الشديد.
I'll confiscate all of them then.
سأصادر كل منهم بعد ذلك.
No!
رقم!
They're my food for thought!
إنهم طعامي للفكر!
They keep me company
يبقونني صحبة
until I sleep every night.
حتى أنام كل ليلة.
How could you be so despicable?
كيف يمكن أن تكون حقيرًا إلى هذا الحد؟
At most, I'll pay you for your portraiture right.
على الأكثر ، سأدفع لك مقابل حق صورتك الشخصية.
Do you think I care about your money?
هل تعتقد أنني أهتم بأموالك؟
Destroy them immediately!
دمرهم على الفور!
No way!
مستحيل!
Stop!
قف!
It's useless for you to destroy them.
لا فائدة من تدميرهم.
I can draw again.
يمكنني الرسم مرة أخرى.
Why don't you
لماذا لا
learn to draw from me?
تعلم الرسم مني؟
That way, you can draw my portraits.
بهذه الطريقة ، يمكنك رسم صوري.
When you learn figure painting,
عندما تتعلم الرسم على الأشكال ،
the most important thing is to understand the figure's bone structure
أهم شيء هو فهم بنية عظام الشكل
and muscle structure,
وهيكل العضلات ،
such as
مثل
their eyebrows,
حواجبهم ،
nose,
الأنف،
lips,
شفه،
♪The road to your heart is so long♪
الطريق إلى قلبك طويل جدًا
and...
و...
their Adam's apple.
تفاحة آدم.
♪Your determination shines on me♪
تصميمك يسطع علي
♪The silly smile on your face♪
♪ الابتسامة السخيفة على وجهك
Weiyi,
وييي ،
do you find
هل تجد
my bone structure beautiful?
هيكل عظمي جميل؟
♪The wandering me is afraid of missing you♪
تجولني خائف من أن أفتقدك
I...
أنا...
I need to use the washroom!
أحتاج إلى استخدام الحمام!
♪My heart has skipped a beat♪
♪ قلبي تخطى خفقان ♪
♪Whose breathing is getting weaker?♪
لمن يضعف تنفسه؟
♪I don't wish to argue who's at fault♪
♪ لا أرغب في مناقشة من هو المخطئ
(This is the figure painting Bai Zeliu wanted.)
(هذه هي اللوحة التي أرادها باي زيليو.)
(I'm sure he will never expect this.)
(أنا متأكد من أنه لن يتوقع هذا أبدًا.)
Come in.
ادخل.
We meet again.
نلتقي مرة أخرى.
Seems like you do like to pester Zeliu.
يبدو أنك تحب مضايقة Zeliu.
Bai Lingfei?
باي لينجفي؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Where's Bai Zeliu?
أين باي زيليو؟
Zeliu is dating the daughter of the chairman of Lvhe Fruit Company.
Zeliu تواعد ابنة رئيس شركة Lvhe Fruit Company.
I was afraid that insensible people might hinder their date.
كنت أخشى أن يعيق الأشخاص غير المدركين موعدهم.
That's why I stayed behind.
لهذا السبب بقيت في الخلف.
A date?
موعد؟
People should know their limitations.
يجب أن يعرف الناس حدودهم.
Although you've been close to Zeliu
على الرغم من أنك كنت قريبًا من Zeliu
for the past few days,
خلال الأيام القليلة الماضية ،
it's common for men
إنه شائع بالنسبة للرجال
to fool around.
يتصرف بحماقة.
In the end, they have to marry someone
في النهاية ، عليهم أن يتزوجوا من شخص ما
with an equal social rank.
بمكانة اجتماعية متساوية.
Your brother and I broke up long ago.
أخيك وأنا انفصلنا منذ فترة طويلة.
That's for the best.
هذا للأفضل.
Now, you're just a sales representative.
الآن ، أنت مجرد مندوب مبيعات.
You're not good enough for him.
أنت لست جيدًا بما يكفي بالنسبة له.
You see,
هل ترى،
we should be clear about our own social rank.
يجب أن نكون واضحين بشأن مرتبتنا الاجتماعية.
Don't you think so,
لا تعتقد ذلك ،
former Young Lady Sun?
سيدة شابة سابقة صن؟
Look.
نظرة.
Your necktie isn't straight.
ربطة العنق ليست مستقيمة.
And here.
و هنا.
There's dust.
هناك غبار.
Liang Wanqing,
ليانغ وانكينغ ،
I've told you many times.
لقد أخبرتك عدة مرات.
I'm not interested in you.
انا لست مثار بالاهتمام بك.
I heard from your sister
سمعت من أختك
that an old woman had been pestering you.
أن امرأة عجوز كانت تزعجك.
That's none of your business.
ليس من شأنك.
But she saw us just now
لكنها رأتنا للتو
and left knowing she couldn't compare with me.
وتركت وهي تعلم أنها لا تستطيع المقارنة معي.
Sun Weiyi,
صن ويي ،
do you know how old you are right now?
هل تعرف كم عمرك الان
Stop hallucinating about the impossible.
توقف عن الهلوسة بشأن المستحيل.
He is a young and talented man
إنه شاب وموهوب
while she is the daughter of a chairman.
وهي ابنة رئيس.
They are
هم انهم
a perfect match.
مباراة ممتازة.
You have no way to compare with her.
ليس لديك طريقة للمقارنة معها.
(Bai Zeliu)
(باي زيليو)
(Add to blacklist)
(أضف إلى القائمة السوداء)